

GABRIELA GUAMÁN

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

gabygm

CONTACT

- **** +593 980 351 58
- paogaby0803@gmail.com
- https://gaby.ec

LANGUAGE

- SpanishEnglish



EDUCATION

- SYSTEMS ENGINEER
 - Universidad Nacional de Loja 2009-2015
- BACHELOR OF MATHEMATICS Instituto Superior Tecnólogico
- "Beatriz Cueva de Ayora" 2002-2008
- AWS CERTIFIED DEVELOPER ASSOCIATE

Amazon Web Services Training and 2020 Certification



SKILLS

- TECHNICAL
- Python Django Java Kotlin
- Git Cl CD AWS Docker
- MysqlPostgresSQLNodeJS
- CONSULTING
- Agile
 Feedback
 Problem Solving



TALKS

LIMPIEZA DE DATOS CON PANDAS

Meet-up Pyladies Ecuador

March 2019

 ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE PRESENT, FUTURE & CHALLENGES

Universidad de las Fuerzas Armadas del Ecuador December 2019

SENTIMENT ANALYSIS

Data day Quito February 2020



ABOUT ME

I am full-stack developer with three years of experience in building web applications, APIs, e-commerce domains. I have also been immersed in mobile application. I define myself as a person who like continuous learning and keeping growing.

In my free time I collaborate in the PyLadies Ecuador and Python Ecuador communities, empowering women in technology and organizing tech events.



EXPERIENCE

Developer Consultant (Thoughtworks)

March 2019-> Present

Ildentity Protection Project

I was part of the pod PEX for three months, this products consist in expose the APIs for parthers and developers for better use of available services.

NodeJSSuperTestApigeeSwagger

Social transformation Project

For three months, I was part of project social transformation in tw, this product heps to empower women and expose the worker's rights in Ecuador.

◆ Android
 ◆ Kotlin
 ◆ Firebase
 ◆ Google Analytics

Prototype Lab

For one month I was part of the team. It consist in a solution for monitoring and managing the maintenance of machinery and equipment, ensuring uninterrupted operations.

◆ AWS IoT
 ◆ Lambda functions
 ◆ CloudWatch

Thoughtworks University

Five weeks intensive training in Xián, China, with the purpose of gain understanding of tw culture and learning the consulting skills for the role of consultant. I also gained technical expertise as a developer and practicing Agile methodologies.

● Java ● Spring Boot ● Selenium

Full-stack (OMINEC)

May 2018 - December 2018

I was in charge of building an electronic billing system according to the standards of Ecuador and I was also responsible for building internal software according to customer needs.

PythonFlaskOdoo

Developer Backend(TIPTI-FULLSTACK)

August 2016 - April 2018

TIPTI is an E-commerce. I was responsible for the development of APIs for the website and mobile application and deployment of applications according with the client specifications.

● Python ● Django ● Postgres ● Heroku ● S3 ● Sentry

Inmobiliaria Pública del Ecuador

Build a website for the offer of public real estate in Ecuador

PythonPostgresDjango

Teacher Computer Maintenance and design(DCA SISTEMAS)

Teach and prepare material for students

Sep. 2015 - Dec. 2017

◆ HTML
 ◆ CSS
 ◆ Illustrator
 ◆ InDesing
 ◆ Premiere
 ◆ Blender

Developer (CIRO SMART TECHNOLOGY) Sep. 2015 - December 2017

Back-end and Fron-end project management reports.

PHPMySQLBootstrap